franchisegator.com 2018-06-26

# Privacy Policy | FranchiseGator.com

### Effective December 14, 2016

At Franchise Gator, LLC ("Franchise Gator"), we only use personal information you provide in the way we specify when we collect it on our website: www.franchisegator.com. We take your privacy seriously, and this policy covers data used in our websites, mobile apps, email and text-messaging services.

Franchise Gator has received TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program. In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program covers only the Web site www.franchisegator.com and does not cover information that may be collected through our mobile apps.

Franchise Gator has also received an **A+ Rating** as a **Better Business Bureau[Accredited Business](http://www.bbb.org/atlanta/business-reviews/franchising/franchise-gator-in-roswell-ga-10000651)**.

We strive to maintain transparency and accountability regarding the collection and use of your personal information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please first contact us at [privacyinfo@franchisegator.com](mailto:privacyinfo@franchisegator.com). If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

#### Our Web Site

All users can view content on our Web site without submitting any personal information (such as name, address, phone number, etc.) to us. However, in order to provide you with a better user experience, we may collect non-personal information from your computer using cookies. More information on this process is below.

#### Mobile Apps and Location Information

When you download or use our mobile apps, you may give permission to share your device's real-time location (from cell towers, GPS, etc.). This information is used to provide services like localized search results. You can disable location-sharing at any time in your device settings. We also use an encrypted version of your device's unique device ID to track app usage, and to send any mobile alerts that you ask you to receive.

#### Our Information Request Form

When you request information from one or more of our Sponsors by submitting your contact information (name, address, phone number, e-mail, etc.) on our registration form, we pass your information only to the businesses that you specify. No other business receives your contact information. Your information, however, is often stored in the receiving company's database, as well as ours. Collected data may be stored in a database outside your home country.

#### Our Newsletter Program

We offer opportunities to register to receive our e-mail newsletter, both in various locations on our Web site and on our Information Request Form. We only add you to our mailing list if you authorize us to. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing our unsubscribe page, or you can contact us at [privacyinfo@franchisegator.com](mailto:privacyinfo@franchisegator.com). Moreover, we do not share your e-mail address or other personal information with other companies unless authorized by you.

#### Our use of tracking technologies

In many cases, we collect non-personal information from your computer using cookies, which are standard Internet technologies used to measure user traffic. For example, cookie data is useful in measuring user visits, browsing patterns, or e-mail message views. This information helps us to provide you with a better user experience by enabling us to compile statistics and measures of user satisfaction, and thereby to continually improve our Web site. Some of this information is collected and compiled by third-party service providers. The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

We employ, as do some of our third party advertising partners, a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information in some instances.

A cookie is a small amount of data that a Web sites server sends to your browser, which is stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be removed from your hard drive. Also, depending on the type and version of web browser you are using, you may be able to change how your computer treats cookies so that cookies are not used or saved. Please check with your browser provider for more information on removing cookies.

Technologies such as tags and scripts are used by Franchise Gator, our advertisers, affiliates, and web analytics service providers  [Google Analytics, Adobe Marketing Cloud Analytics]. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 or Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>.

Our sites and apps also participate in the Adobe Marketing Cloud Device Co-op to better understand how you use our website and apps across the various devices you use, and to deliver tailored promotions. Learn more [https://cross-device-privacy.adobe.com](https://cross-device-privacy.adobe.com/) about how Adobe does this and how you can opt-out of this if you so wish.

#### Behavioral Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the pupose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [**here**](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

To opt-out of interest-based ads on Google, go to [www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) and make a selection next to "Opt-Out Settings" to prevent targeted advertising on Google's own sites, or across the web.

To opt-out of interest-based ads on Facebook, go to [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) in the USA, [Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada](http://youradchoices.ca/) in Canada or the [European Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) in Europe and select "Facebook Inc." from the list.

#### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may, however, provide your personal information to companies that provides services to help us with our business activities, such as analytics and web metric services. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary_ to provide these services to us.

#### Special cases

In a limited number of cases, we may choose to share either personal or non-personal information with third-parties. Such examples are subpoenas, court orders, bankruptcy proceedings or other requests to cooperate with other types of legal enforcement.

#### Business Transfers

As we continue to develop our business we might sell or buy companies, subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information is generally one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the event that we are acquired or assigned, customer information will be one of the transferred assets. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

#### Links to third parties

Although Franchise Gator provides links to other sites that may provide valuable information, we cannot control how they collect or manage personal information from their Web sites. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and data collection procedures.

#### Security measures

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. While no data transfer can be completely secure, we will make reasonable efforts to secure your data while being transferred, stored or processed. Additionally, we require all third party service providers to mitigate security risks by implementing their own security program with proportional safeguards. We also require that they notify us when/if they discover a privacy or security breach involving personal information received from us, and we require them to take immediate steps to correct or address the security failure that caused the breach. Lastly, for any third party services we use, we review their terms of use and privacy policies annually to ensure they comply with our obligations to our users.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us at [privacyinfo@franchisegator.com](mailto:privacyinfo@franchisegator.com) if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, at which point we remove your information from our active database. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Testimonials

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our website in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacyinfo@franchisegator.com](mailto:privacyinfo@franchisegator.com).

#### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Single Sign-On

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

#### Children's privacy

Franchise Gator is intended to be used by individuals over the age of 18. We do not seek or willingly collect information on children under the age of 18. If we discover that we have collected information on a child under the age of 13, then we will delete that information from our system.

#### Updates and Effective Date

We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason. Any modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting, unless otherwise indicated. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this Web site prior to the change becoming effective, typically 30 days in advance. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you are aware of the information we collect, how we use it and to whom we consent to disclose it.

#### Additional information

We need your assistance in keeping your information up to date. If you would like to review, correct or change your personal information or need assistance unsubscribing, please email us at [privacyinfo@franchisegator.com](mailto:privacyinfo@franchisegator.com) or write to us at the address below. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

#### Frequently Asked Questions

To view the answers to some common questions, please visit our FAQ Page.

#### Privacy Coordinator

**Franchise Gator**  
599 W. Crossville Road, Suite 200  
Roswell, GA 30075
